Personal Info

- □ saba.marzoughi18@gmail.com
- & LinkedIn
- % GitHub
- (\$ Iran Tehran

Fatemeh (Saba) Marzoughi

Front-end Developer
React & React Native

About me

I'm a Software Engineer with a passion for Frontend. I have been practicing for 5 years now, and I believe I'm ready for my next challenge where I can develop beautiful mobile applications and contribute to creation of a great software engineering team.

Skills

- HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript,
 TypeScript
- React
- React Native (Android, iOS)
- Electron (Windows, Mac OS)
- Rest-API, GraphQL
- Redux, Context
- Native-Base, MUI
- Jest
- Realm, Hive
- Functional programming, OOP
- Strapi CMS, TestFlight
- Postman, Jira, Figma, Agile/Scrum team, Git, GitHub

Education

(Sep 2017- Dec 2021)

Diploma: Bachelor of Computer Engineering (Software)

University: Islamic Azad University, Tehran-Central branch

Work Experiences

• <u>UniPlato</u>: Mid-Level Front-End Developer

Australia (Remote), Aug 2022 – May 2023, <u>Visit Project</u>

- Brought the "Coffee" platform to its next level by building its desktop Mac Application using Electron and released over 20 versions of the app to TestFlight.
- Improved code base by building over 15 pixel-perfect, responsive, and clean **React** components which could be used by other team members in all the modules as our design system.
- Brought over 20 new features with demos to the platform by communicating with team members and using REST-API, web sockets, and working with both functional and classbased components using React Library.
- Improved the stability of the platform by reviewing new team members' codes.
- Upgraded the platform by refactoring the old code structures of 2 old modules and bringing them back to the project.
- Comfortel: Mid-Level Front-End Developer

Russia (Remote), Dec 2021 – May 2022, Visit Project

- Increased the usability of the "Techpal" platform by releasing its desktop app on 3 operating systems (Windows, Mac, and Linux) using Electron and its Android app using React-Native.
- Enhanced the team communication by customizing Mattermost platform both for desktop (Windows, Mac, and Linux) and mobile apps (Android).
- o Had experience using Flutter.
- Open Source and Freelancing: Front-End Developer
 Tehran (Remote), Apr 2020 Dec 2021, Visit Project
 - "MyPlayer" is an open-source React Native project using TypeScript, available on both iOS and Android which is a Video and Audio player with over 20 features on it.
 - Improved the portfolio of Bytino startup team by working on 2 open-source projects and linking them to the team webpage.